fxinco.com 2015-06-06

# 

                                                                     Privacy Policy
               This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which PEGASUS MARKETS LIMITED collects, uses,
               maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the
               http://www.pgmarkets.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all
               products and services offered by PEGASUS MARKETS LIMITED.
               Personal           identification        information
               We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including,
               but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter,
               respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features
               or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name,
               email address, mailing address, phone number. We will collect personal identification
               information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can
               always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent
               them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
               Non - personal              identification      information
               We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact
               with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the
               type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site,
               such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar
               information.
               Web browser                 cookies
               Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies
               on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about
               them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when
               cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function
               properly.
               How we use collected                    information
               PEGASUS MARKETS LIMITED may collect and use Users personal information for the
               following purposes:
               - To improve customer service
               Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support
               needs more efficiently.
               - To personalize user experience
               We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the
               services and resources provided on our Site.
               - To improve our Site
               We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
               - To process payments
Level 1, Dickens Street 1, Napier 4110, New Zealand           pgmarkets@pgmarkets.com
www.pgmarkets.com                                             +64 6 833 6654
                                                                                                                 M A R K E T S

               We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to
               provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to
               the extent necessary to provide the service.
               - To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature
               To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to
               them.
               - To send periodic emails
               We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their
               order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If
               User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company
               news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like
               to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.
               How we protect your information
               We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security
               measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your
               personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our
               Site.
               Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL
               secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
               Sharing your personal                   information
               We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may
               share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification
               information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and
               advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
               Compliance               with children’s      online privacy protection act
               Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never
               collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 18, and no
               part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.
               Changes            to this privacy policy
               PEGASUS MARKETS LIMITED has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time.
               When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page and send you an
               email. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed
               about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge
               and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become
               aware of modifications.
               Your acceptance                  of these terms
               By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do
               not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following
               the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
               Contact us
               If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your
               dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Level 1, Dickens Street 1, Napier 4110, New Zealand          pgmarkets@pgmarkets.com
www.pgmarkets.com                                            +64 6 833 6654
                                                                                                              M A R K E T S

                PEGASUS MARKETS LIMITED
                http://www.pgmarkets.com
                Level 1, Dickens Street 1, Napier 4110
                pgmarkets@pgmarkets.com
                This document was last updated on July 09, 2014
Level 1, Dickens Street 1, Napier 4110, New Zealand pgmarkets@pgmarkets.com
www.pgmarkets.com                                   +64 6 833 6654
                                                                            M A R K E T S
